Why am I moving all the freaking time?
Yeah, let me just hang my towel up there.
All these piles finally sorted.
Good morning, guys.
Happy New Year.
It is the last day and my last morning in this apartment.
It's another moving day, and it is going to be a big one because I'm truly moving everything out of this place.
I have movers on the way, my dad's on the way, my boyfriend's here to help, and I just kind of feel crazy that I'm moving out of
this place because when I first moved here, I was at such like a low point in my life.
But it's right at the time where I was retaking a course that I failed, and I wasn't even close at passing.
But yeah, I'm finally moving out of this place.
You can see I've taken everything off the walls now, and almost everything is packed.
So without further ado, let's get into this video.
So this is the front door, and immediately when you walk in, there's this long hallway and a ton of closets, so just bear with me.
When I open this closet, it's a kind of an awkward shape, and there's like no built-in, so I'm probably just going to put cleaning supplies
there, and then this closet is just the coat closet because it has a built-in rack, and then I'm also going to put my shoe storage here as
well, and then this door leads to the bathroom.
This is the bathroom.
It smells like cleaning supplies in here.
They actually gave us a rod already, so I'm just gonna hang my shower curtain, and it actually has a tub, which was one of my non-negotiables.
Has this massive mirror, and these ceilings are so tall, guys, like I feel so small compared to this door, and then this closet is boring.
It's just the heater and like water tank, and then finally the last closet.
This closet is just the laundry room.
It has obviously the washer and dryer on one side, and it's really nice that they left these built-ins, and I think I'm gonna use this built-in for
cleaning products, linens, and then also PR.
And then now for the living room.
This is what really sold me on this place.
I love the hardwood floor.
I love how spacious it is and how tall the ceilings are.
And then this is obviously the kitchen.
We've started moving in already.
And so then this is the kitchen, and right beside it is this little like area that I'm probably gonna make my office.
Because when I was touring this place, the last tenant had three desks here.
One work desk, a craft desk, and then I think their partner's desk.
I'm gonna be living alone in this place by myself, but I do love having a crafting area, so I think I'm gonna put desks here just right
here by these windows, and then I'm probably gonna put a bookshelf or something or another on this wall, maybe my mug shelf that I got for Christmas.
This is another view of the kitchen.
Please ignore my massive monitor.
There's full-size appliances, which is really nice.
They cleaned out everything, which I always appreciate.
It's just the this, and then this is another view of the living room from the kitchen, and then this is a little housewarming gift that I got
from my landlord, and honestly has all the essentials that you need for when you're moving in, things that are just like packed away like toilet
paper, paper towel, microfiber cloths, kleenex, there's hand soap, dish soap, toilet cleaner, and pods and command hooks, which is just so perfect.
And then beside the kitchen, I have my bedroom, which doesn't have any windows, but I do really love how spacious it is and how cozy I can
make it.
There's light coming in from the top, and then there is a massive closet right here, which I'm so excited for.
This is the other view of the bedroom out to the living room.
It has these glass sliding doors, but that doesn't really provide any privacy, so this is what it looks like when both the glass doors are closed
together.
It's like a little cube here, and for the two glass doors, my plan is to just put some like privacy screens on it like frosted glass or
just like hang some curtains on the inside of them for some privacy because my room is always a mess and of Course, I don't want guests to
see that, so it's a plan for right now.
Now, I know some of you guys are probably wondering why am I moving all the freaking time.
If you been following along, I've moved seven times in the last three years, and that is a lot of moving vlogs, okay?
And it honestly just boils down to my university, the program that I'm enrolled in, which is pharmacy school.
The program itself just does not follow a regular calendar school year or like a regular school year, so I'm in between cities a lot because I choose
to do my internships closer to family, which means that I have to move everything to go stay at a new place to be closer to my
job, and then obviously when school is in session, I have to move back here.
So that is why I have made this really big move, and in 2026, I'm going to be in pharmacy school for eight months, and this year it
does follow a normal school year, so January to April and September to December, I will be in school.
And so now this place is closer to my university, and it's going to be really easy for me to go to and from school.
But yeah, hopefully that gives you guys some context as to why I'm moving all the time.
It's totally not up to me.
I would love to stop moving so often.
Boxes are finally arriving from the movers.
I think this is the last of them because this is literally taking up the entire living room.
I'm going
to
go to the bathroom.
Thank you.
Of course, I've unpacked my Jelly Cat, so I have Woody here, which is my jumbo woodland bunny.
She's gonna go here.
Please ignore this mess, but I have also packed all the jellies in this drawer.
There's so many.
I'm just wondering which ones I should add to the bed now.
I'm gonna take out these two guys because I think this one's super cute, and then this one because it was super snowy today.
Okay guys, I just took a much needed shower.
The good news is the water pressure is really great here, and I like the shower head.
But the spout is kind of doing this like weird thing where water is coming out of the bottom and the top at the same time.
So I'm gonna have to ask my landlord to take a look at that.
The mirror here is also massive.
I have to show you guys this, like, excuse the mess.
I've literally been living here for four hours.
But this mirror goes all the way up to the ceiling, or almost, and the ceilings are like 12 to 14 feet tall.
So this is just massive, and on that note, do you notice anything else funny?
Look, look at that.
How am I supposed to get that like up there?
Like, it's zoomed in, but this is it in context.
Yeah, let me just hang my towel up there.
Hello!
But anyways, it is my first night here and essentially the start of a new year.
So I just did an everything shower, and then I also washed all the sheets and like duvet covers, pillowcases.
Essentially all of my linens and towels, including like the floor ones.
I just know that I'm going to sleep so well with all those kinds of things done.
But tomorrow, I really need to tackle the kitchen because I haven't opened a single one of those boxes, and all the appliances and all the dishware are
still tucked away.
Good
morning guys, I just had my first
night in the apartment, and it was so nice.
I actually slept super well, and I feel like I always do after an everything shower and once all the linens are freshly laundered.
I will say though, it is a little bit noisy, and I think it's because of all the vents in the place, and my dad was actually warning
me about this yesterday when he was talking about like there are multiple vents by the windows, and they travel like 40 feet across the entire
place, and the bedroom doesn't have walls that go all the way up to let in light, so you can kind of hear everything.
But that aside, I slept really well.
I placed a grocery order.
I just brought those in, and I also got a mop because I don't have a welcome mat yet, so I've been kind of tracking in a little
bit of salt near the front door, so I'm going to tackle that after breakfast.
I'm going to go to bed now.
I'm going to.
Go to bed now.
Wow.
Is that two or one?
Oh my god.
Like, do you guys hear that?
That's the heater running.
That's what I was hearing all night when I was sleeping.
It was kind of like white noise, but I don't really like sleeping with white noise, so...
Yeah.
So, do you know if there is enough space?
I'm sure it'll be a good idea.
Oh my god.
Huh?
Uh-oh.
First matcha I've made in the apartment, so let's do a taste test.
Oh my god, I've been running around so much during the holidays that I haven't been making these.
This is definitely the fix I needed.
I'm now tackling all of my clothing, but the closet is super massive, so I'm really excited to just put everything away.
Those pants are still drying, so that's why they're hung like that, but I also did, I did have time to go and do my drawers though.
So these are all my regular bras, so they have the straps, and I just sorted them by color, and then these ones are
colorful, and then I have the strapless bras in the top, and I try to match these in terms of color.
So these are just my workout sets, and then these are just miscellaneous workout sets and pilates socks, and then in this drawer I've just put matching PJ
sets here, and then some didn't fit into this like divider box I have, and then I have some sleep t-shirts here, and I try to sort the
t-shirts by color.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
The bluebirds be supposed to sing
along that I love you.
Oh, I walk the street where I was born.
Very safe here.
Oh, I just want to lie down on the bed.
I'm so tired.
I'm trying to sign up for gym to lose weight, and it's on.
I'm low.
Please, guys.
I always dream of having a place at my home.
What do you mean?
You literally have a house.
Hey guys, my parents have finally left, and I've just washed up from dinner.
It was my brother's birthday, so I just went home, and they offered to drive me up, and then obviously I invited both my parents to come in.
My mom was picking through my PR, and then my dad just got straight to work, and he was like doing my dishes in the
sink, and I was trying to tell him to relax, but if any of your guys' dads' love language is acts of service, you know that they just
like never sit down and relax, I feel.
They're always just doing something, and especially every single time I move, my dad's like crushing boxes or taking out the garbage, and that kind of thing.
So obviously I'm super grateful for both of them, and we have another busy day unpacking tomorrow.
So I will see you guys in the morning.
Time to build some bar stools.
Pushing this and dragging this through the entire lobby.
It was literally a humiliation ritual, so now let's build these guys.
Ouch!
Oh my god, I hate my life.
Okay, this was actually not that hard to build, and now we're going to do a sit test because I'm not sure if these are going to be...
They're okay.
They're not that comfortable, but at least it's done.
And it wasn't that bad.
Ooh, they kind of wiggle.
Hey guys, I've been working on
the closet for three hours, and I feel like I can finally show you what I've got going on.
I was also just on the phone with Ara, and she said that it looks like the back room of a clothing store, which I will take as
a compliment.
This is what it looks like right now.
I've put up all of my different sweaters.
I tried to color coordinate them.
These ones are all my Cezanne sweaters, so that's why they have their own pile.
And I've gone through my pants box, so that's why I have all these piles finally sorted.
On the top level, I have my really, really big baggy jeans, and then some work skirts because I don't really wear these piles a
lot, and then the second shelf is the most accessible, so I put my work pants and then my everyday style of jeans, so mostly straight cut barrel
jeans, a little bit of flare.
Bottom layer, I just have some comfy PJs, and I also try to color coordinate them, and lastly, I've sorted all of my...
White tank tops into this organizer.
Now it is time for a good old journal sesh.
I'm gonna be honest, I haven't journaled in the new year yet.
It's already like January 4th, I believe, so I am already behind on making my official New Year's resolutions and goal setting, because when it's written down in
the journal, it's essentially written in stone.
So yeah, I'm just gonna do this for the next like half hour, and then I think I really need to go to bed.
Thank you.